YUSRIL AHMAD SOFYAN

sofyanyusrilahmad@gmail.com | (+62) 813-9311-6363 | linkedin.com/in/yusrilahmadsofyan/

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

I am a Visual Communication Design student with experience as a designer during my internship. Throughout the internship, I have honed my skills in various Adobe applications, including Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro, and After Effects. I possess strong technical skills in creating visually appealing designs and layouts. Additionally, my involvement in campus committees has developed my soft skills in teamwork, effective collaboration, logical and methodical thinking, as well as strong analytical and creative abilities.

EDUCATION

Telkom University 2021 – Present

Bachelor of Visual Communication Design – GPA 3.77

- Head of strategic review and action department of BEM FIK 2022
- Staff of strategic review and action department of BEM FIK 2021
- intern staff of Multimedia Division of BEM FIK 2020

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer | PT. New Borneo Resource

26 February 2024 - Present

Responsible for managing the company's visual media strategy, focusing on positive branding and a deep understanding of the needs and aspirations of the communities served. deep understanding of the needs and aspirations of the communities served. With using visual media platforms.

Second assistant | CV. Rizki Bangun

1 July 2022 - Present

Joining the family business, which specializes in blasting. My role involves creating captivating and relevant visual content for our digital marketing campaigns, primarily on social media platforms such as Facebook.

Social media Specialist | @ministryofidol

27 June, 2023 – 28 December 2023

Responsible for managing all the visual assets required for their performances, from posters, photography, and Instagram feeds so that each of their performances can be presented in the best way possible. from posters, photography, and instagram feeds so that each of their performances can be presented in a attractively and professionally to loyal fans.

Caster & Kordinator Broadcast | PERAGA FIK 2022

26 February 2024 - Present

As a Caster and head of the Broadcast division at the creative industry faculty sports week (PERAGA FIK 2022), an event organized by BEM Faculty of Creative Industries in the form of an e-sport tournament. Responsible for to provide in-depth commentary and analysis of the e-sport tournament as well as ensuring an exciting and informative viewing experience. provide an exciting and informative viewing experience for the audience.

COMMITTEE

Coordinator of Logistics Division - OASIS 2022

- Obtaining permission for equipment and venue borrowing
- Setting up a large meeting space
- Designing the layout of prospect activities
- Successful recruitment of equipment vendors

Field Coordinator - Basic Leadership Training for the Faculty of Creative Industries 2022

- Ensuring the smooth running of the event
- Supervising event participants
- Checking and maintaining cleanliness in the work area

ACHIEVEMENT

Staff of The Month, Appreciation for the Best Staff Performance in the 2022 Student Executive Body of the Faculty of Creative Industries.

SKILLS

Hard Skill: Design – Advanced, Language – Advanced, Project Management – Intermediate, Research – Intermediate, Communication - Intermediate

Soft skill: Creative, Critical Thinking, Public Speaking, Teamwork, Collaboration

Tools: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe After Effect, Corel Draw, Figma, Canva.

SOCIAL MEDIA

Linkedin: Yusril Ahmad Sofyan | Instagram: @ya.sofyan | Pinterest: yusrilahmadsofyan

PORTOFOLIO

http://bit.ly/sofyanporto